A Guide to Dr. Vamik D. Volkan Papers
Claude Moore Health Sciences Library
- Vamik D.Volkan's Paper: "The 'Crucial Jucture': The Intrapsychic Story of Integration in a Borderline Patient", ND, TD (Box-folder 005:014)
- Vamik D.Volkan's Paper: "Schizophrenia: primitive Object Relationship in Treatment" ND, TD (Box-folder 005:015)
- Vamik D.Volkan's Paper: "Large-group and Individual Identities," German, in book "Identitat und Konflikt: Individuelle, ethnische und institutionelle Aspekte der Identitat (Identity and Conflict: Individual, Ethnic and Institutional Aspects of Identity) Edited by Axel Schuler-Schneider with contributions by Vamik D. Volkan and Stavros Mentzos, ND, TD (Box-folder 005:016)
- Review of Vamik Volkan's Book, [Primitive Internationlized Object Relations], 1978, TD (Box-folder 005:017)
- Review of Vamik Volkan's Book, [Cyprus: War and Adaptation], 1979, TD (Box-folder 005:018)
- Review of Vamik Volkan's Book, [Linking Objects abd Linking Phenomena Adaptation], 1981, TD (Box-folder 005:019)
- Review of Vamik Volkan's Book, [What Do You Get When You Cross A Dandelion With A Rose?], 1984, TD (Box-folder 005:020)
- Review of Vamik Volkan's Book, [The Immortal Ataturk], 1984, TD (Box-folder 005:021)
- Review of Vamik Volkan's Book, [Six Steps in the Treatment of Borderline Personality Organization], 1987, TD (Box-folder 005:022)
- Review of Vamik Volkan's Paper, [Treatment of Complicated Mourning], 1988(5), TD (Box-folder 005:023)
- Review of Vamik Volkan's Book, [The Need to Have Enemies and Allies], 1988, TD (Box-folder 005:024)
- Review of Vamik Volkan's Book, [Attitudes of Entitlement: Theoretical and Clinical Issue], 1988, TD (Box-folder 005:025)
- Review of Vamik Volkan's Book, [The Psychodynamics of International Relationships, Vol. I, II], 1990/1991, TD (Box-folder 005:026)
- Review of Vamik Volkan's Book, [The Homosexualities: Reality, Fantasy, and Arts], 1991, TD (Box-folder 005:027)
- Review of Vamik Volkan's Book, [The Homosexualities and the Therapeutic Process], 1991, TD (Box-folder 005:028)
- Review of Vamik Volkan's Book, [Eine Borderline Therapie], 1992, TD (Box-folder 005:029)
- Review of Vamik Volkan's Book, [Life After Loss: The Lesson of Grief], 1992, TD (Box-folder 005:030)
- Review of Vamik Volkan's Book, [turks and Greeks: Neighbors in Conflict], 1995, TD (Box-folder 005:031)
- Review of Vamik Volkan's Book, [The Infantile Psychotic Self], 1995, TD (Box-folder 005:032)
- Review of Vamik Volkan's Book, [Bloodline: From Ethnic Pride to Ethnic Terrorism], 1997, TD (Box-folder 005:033)
- Review of Vamik Volkan's Book, [Siblings in the Unconscious and Psychopathology], 1997, TD (Box-folder 005:034)
- Review of Vamik Volkan's Book, [Richard Nixon], 1997, TD (Box-folder 005:035)
- Review of Vamik Volkan's Book, [Even Paranoids Have Enemies], 1998, TD (Box-folder 005:036)
- Review of Vamik Volkan's Book,[The Seed of Madness: Constitution, Environment, and Fantasy in the Organization of the Psychotic Core], 1998, TD (Box-folder 005:037)
- Announcement of Vamik Volkan's Book, [Cyprus and Its People], 1998, TD (Box-folder 005:038)
- Review of Vamik Volkan's Book, [Das Versagen der Diplomatie], 1999, TD (Box-folder 005:039)
- Review of Vamik Volkan's Book, [Blind Trust: Large Group and Their Leaders in Times of Crisis and Terror], 2004, TD (Box-folder 005:040)
- Nobel Peace Prize Recommendation for Vamik D. Volkan by Nicholas J. Delva, 2005, TD (Box-folder 006:001)
- Nobel Peace Prize Recommendation for Vamik D. Volkan by Stephen David Kaplan, 2005, TD (Box-folder 006:002)
- Nobel Peace Prize Recommendation for Vamik D. Volkan by John R. Lineweaver, 2005, TD (Box-folder 006:003)
- Nobel Peace Prize Recommendation for Vamik D. Volkan by Jon Copper, 2005, TD (Box-folder 006:004)
- Nobel Peace Prize Recommendation for Vamik D. Volkan by Paul J. Fink, 2005, TD (Box-folder 006:005)
- Nobel Peace Prize Recommendation for Vamik D. Volkan by Newell Fischer, 2005, TD (Box-folder 006:006)
- Nobel Peace Prize Recommendation for Vamik D. Volkan by Allan King, 2005, TD (Box-folder 006:007)
- Nobel Peace Prize Recommendation for Vamik D. Volkan by Edward R. Shapiro, 2005, TD (Box-folder 006:008)
- Nobel Peace Prize Recommendation for Vamik D. Volkan by David R. Rothstein, 2005, TD (Box-folder 006:009)
- Nobel Peace Prize Recommendation for Vamik D. Volkan by Norman Itzkowitz, 2005, TD (Box-folder 006:010)
- Nobel Peace Prize Recommendation for Vamik D. Volkan by Johannes Lehtonen, 2005, TD (Box-folder 006:011)
- Nobel Peace Prize Recommendation for Vamik D. Volkan by Fern Cramer Azima, 2005, TD (Box-folder 006:012)
- Nobel Peace Prize Recommendation for Vamik D. Volkan by Howard F. Stein, 2005, TD (Box-folder 006:013)
- Nobel Peace Prize Recommendation for Vamik D. Volkan by Ilany Kogan, 2005, TD (Box-folder 006:014)
- Nobel Peace Prize Recommendation for Vamik D. Volkan by Bernd Baumgartl, 2005, TD (Box-folder 006:015)
- Nobel Peace Prize Recommendation for Vamik D. Volkan by Salman Akhtar, 2005, TD (Box-folder 006:016)
- Nobel Peace Prize Recommendation for Vamik D. Volkan by Anne Lindhardt, 2005, TD (Box-folder 006:017)
- Nobel Peace Prize Recommendation for Vamik D. Volkan by Freud Conference Organizing Committee, 2005, TD (Box-folder 006:018)
- Nobel Peace Prize Recommendation for Vamik D. Volkan by Eduard Klain, 2005, TD (Box-folder 006:019)
- Nobel Peace Prize Recommendation for Vamik D. Volkan by Peter Loewenberg, 2005, TD (Box-folder 006:020)
- Nobel Peace Prize Recommendation for Vamik D. Volkan by, 2005, TD (Box-folder 006:021)
- Nobel Peace Prize Recommendation for Vamik D. Volkan by Evelin Gerda Lindner, 2005, TD (Box-folder 006:022)
- Nobel Peace Prize Recommendation for Vamik D. Volkan by Thomas J. Scheff, 2005, TD (Box-folder 006:023)
- Nobel Peace Prize Recommendation for Vamik D. Volkan by Jaan Kaplinski, 2005, TD (Box-folder 006:024)
- Nobel Peace Prize Recommendation for Vamik D. Volkan by Nodar Sarjveladze, Manana Gabashvili, Nino Makhashvili and Darejan Jana Javakhishvili, 2005, TD (Box-folder 006:025)
- Nobel Peace Prize Recommendation for Vamik D. Volkan by Malcolm Pines, 2005, TD (Box-folder 006:026)
- Nobel Peace Prize Recommendation for Vamik D. Volkan by Ivan Urlic, 2005, TD (Box-folder 006:027)
- Nobel Peace Prize Recommendation for Vamik D. Volkan by Wolf Werdigier, 2005, TD (Box-folder 006:028)
- Basic Data on Dr. Vamik Volkan for the Nobel Peace Prize Recommendation, 2005, TD (Box-folder 006:029)
- Nobel Peace Prize Recommendation for Vamik D. Volkan by Rector of the University of Ankara, Turkey, 2007, TD (Box-folder 006:030)
- Nobel Peace Prize Recommendation for Vamik D. Volkan by Amb Aktan, 2007, TD (Box-folder 006:031)
- Nobel Peace Prize Recommendation for Vamik D. Volkan by Kenan Atakol, 2007, TD (Box-folder 006:032)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Newspaper Article: "Ambassador at Monticello", 1970(2/12), Newspaper Clipping (Box-folder 006:033)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Newspaper Article: "Menninger Director to Speak", 1970(2/24), Newspaper Clipping (Box-folder 006:034)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Newspaper Article: "Turkish Cypriots' Bird Raising in the 1960s Held Escape Value", 1973(2/11), Newspaper Article (Box-folder 006:035)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Newspaper Article: "UVa Psychiatrist Treats Failure to Cope with Death", 1973(4/15), Newspaper Article (Box-folder 006:036)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Newspaper Article: "Regriefing Therapy", 1973(6/18), Newspaper Article (Box-folder 006:037)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Newspaper Article: "Gay Definition Battle Brewing", 1974(6/21), Newspaper Article (Box-folder 006:038)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Newspaper Articles: "Prof. Vamik Volkan Kibris'ta", 1975(7/17), Newspaper Clippings (Box-folder 006:039)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Newspaper Articles: "Adaptation to Social Changes" lecture at Saray hotel in Nicosia, Northern Cyprus, 1975(7/31), Newspaper Clippings (Box-folder 006:040)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Newspaper Article: "Volkan Accepts Post As Blue Ridge Medical Director", 1983-1984, Newspaper Clipping (Box-folder 006:041)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Magazine Article by Ahmet C. Gazioglu about Volkan's new book, "Cyprus - War and Adaptation," 1979(7/16), Newspaper Article (Box-folder 006:042)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Magazine Article: "Narcissistic Grandiosity is What A Department Chairman Shares with Ataturk", 1979(11/12), Newspaper Article (Box-folder 006:043)
  Letters, Reports
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Newspaper Article: "Professor Aids Turks", 1981(9/3), Newspaper Article (Box-folder 006:044)
  Reports
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Newspaper Article: "Psychiatrist Finds His Past in Present", 1981(10), Newspaper Clipping (Box-folder 006:045)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Newspaper Article: "Using 'Magical' Momentos to Transcend Grief", 1981(10/4), Newspaper Clipping (Box-folder 006:046)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Newspaper Article: "Volkan's Speak on the Psychological Effects of Mourning", 1981(11/20), Newspaper Clipping (Box-folder 006:047)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - "Washington Post" Newspaper Article: For the Record: "Guess That Makes It Easier to Decide", 1981(12/6), Newspaper Clipping (Box-folder 006:048)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Newspaper Article: "Mourning is Necessary in Overcoming Grief", 1982(1/31), Newspaper Clipping (Box-folder 006:049)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Newspaper Article: "Volkan's Interest in Bereavement", 1982(2), Newspaper Clipping (Box-folder 006:050)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Magazine Article: "The Psychiatry in the Arab Israeli Conflict" 1982(5/2), Newspaper Clipping (Box-folder 006:051)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - "Hurriyet" (Turkish daily newspaper) newspaper article on the 25th Ankara Medical School class reunion, Atlanta, Georgia, 1982(8/24), Newspaper Clipping (Box-folder 006:052)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Newspaper Articles: "New Life for Blue Ridge", 1983(5/9), Newspaper Clipping (Box-folder 006:053)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Newsletter Article: "Volkan, Elected President of the International Society of Political Psychology", 1982(5), Newsletter Article (Box-folder 006:054)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Magazine Article: "Volkan as President of the International Society of Political Psychology", 1983(12), Magazine Article (Box-folder 006:055)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Magazine Article: "Group Therapy for the Middle East", 1984(6/24), Magazine Clipping (Box-folder 006:056)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Newspaper Article: "Importance of Having Enemies Stressed", 1984(8/23), Newspaper Clipping (Box-folder 006:057)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Newspaper Articles: "Everyone Needs Foes", 1984(8/26), Newspaper Article (Box-folder 006:058)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Newspaper Article: "Our Enemies Are Just As Our Friends", 1984(9/12), Newspaper Article (Box-folder 006:059)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Newspaper Article: "Listening At Start Seems Key to International Talks", 1985(1/13), Newspaper Clipping (Box-folder 006:060)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Magazine Article: "Letter From the Director of Blue Ridge Hospital", 1985(2/20), Newsletter (Box-folder 006:061)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Magazine Articles: "In Defense of the Mind", 1985(spring), Magazine Articles (Box-folder 006:062)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Newspaper Article: "Psychological Factors Affect Arm Race", 1985(4/28), Newspaper Clipping (Box-folder 006:063)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Magazine Articles: "Publication Announcement - The Immortal Ataturk", 1985(5/1-11), Magazine Clippings (Box-folder 006:064)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Newspaper Article: "Psychological View on the Arms Race", 1986(10/6), Newspaper Clipping (Box-folder 006:065)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Newspaper Article: "The Healing Gift of Forgiveness", 1987(6/14), Newspaper Clipping (Box-folder 006:066)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Newspaper Article: "Study of Normal Mourning Process Illuminates Grief Gone Awry", 1988(3/29), Newspaper Clippings (Box-folder 006:067)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Newsletter Article: "Center to Study the Mind and Human Interaction", 1988(12/19), Newsletter Article (Box-folder 006:068)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Magazine Articles: "Peace - A State of Mind", 1989(Spring), Magazine Articles (Box-folder 006:069)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Magazine Article: "Speaking with Dr. Vamik D. Volkan", 1989(3), Magazine Article (Box-folder 006:070)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Magazine Article: "Why We All Love to Hate", 1989(8/28), Magazine Clipping (Box-folder 006:071)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Newspaper Articles: "The Right to Hear and Be Heard", 1989(11/19), Newspaper Clippings (Box-folder 006:072)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - "Savon Sanomat" (Finnish newspaper) newspaper article regarding an interview with Volkan in regard to his visit at Kuopio University, 1986, Newspaper Clippings (Box-folder 006:073)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Newspaper Article: Society Mourn Loss of Old Order, U.S. Laments Change, 1990(7/22), Newspaper Clipping (Box-folder 006:074)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Newspaper Article: Enemies List Getting Shorter: Some Hate It, 1990(8/1), Newspaper Clippings (Box-folder 006:075)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Newspaper Article: 1990(11/28), Newspaper Article (Box-folder 006:076)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Newspaper Article: "Psykologiasta Apua Konflikteihin"1991, Newspaper Article (Box-folder 006:077)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Newspaper Article: "Saddam Driven by Grandeur", 1991(2/21), Newspaper Clippings (Box-folder 006:078)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Newspaper Article: 1991(7/5), Newspaper Article (Box-folder 006:079)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Newspaper Article: 1991(7/5), Newspaper Article (Box-folder 006:080)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Newspaper Article: 1991(7/27), Newspaper Article (Box-folder 006:081)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Newspaper Article: 1991(7/27), Newspaper Articles (Box-folder 006:082)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Newspaper Article: 1991(8/16), Newspaper Article (Box-folder 006:083)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Newspaper Article: "Coup Failed to Revive Past Power", 1991(8/26), Newspaper Clippings (Box-folder 006:084)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Newspaper Article: 1991(9/18), Newspaper Article (Box-folder 006:085)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Newspaper Article: "Psychiatric Team Easing Tensions", 1991(11/25), Newspaper Article (Box-folder 006:086)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Newspaper Article: 1992(2/7), Newspaper Article (Box-folder 006:087)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Newspaper Article: 1992(3-5), Newspaper Clippings (Box-folder 006:088)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Newspaper Article: "White-Hat Diplomacy", 1992(5/9), Newspaper Clipping (Box-folder 006:089)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Newspaper Article: 1993(11/21), Newspaper Clippings (Box-folder 006:090)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Newspaper Article: "Sense of Threat Called A Catalyst", 1992(12/14), Newspaper Clippings (Box-folder 006:091)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Newspaper Article: "World In Grip of Ethnic Strife As Cold War Barriers Drop", 1992(12/15), Newspaper Article (Box-folder 006:092)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Newspaper Article: "Adversaries Create Devils of Each Other", 1992(12/15), Newspaper Clippings (Box-folder 007:001)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Newspaper Articles: "Seeking the Framework for a Disjointed World", 1992(12/16), Newspaper Articles (Box-folder 007:002)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Newspaper Article: "A Chance to Purge the Poison Assembing for the Greater Good", 1992-1993, Newspaper Article (Box-folder 007:003)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Newspaper Article: "Ethnic Hatred on the Loose", 1993, Newspaper Article (Box-folder 007:004)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Newspaper Article: "Group Lifts Inner Barriers to Piece", 1993(1/10), Newspaper Article (Box-folder 007:005)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Magazine Article: "Mikhail Gorbachev to Help Celebrate Jefferson's Birthday", 1993(3), Magazine Article (Box-folder 007:006)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Newspaper Article: 1993(3/6), Newspaper Article (Box-folder 007:007)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Magazine Article: "Putting Countries on the Couch", 1993(4/22), Magazine Clipping (Box-folder 007:008)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Newspaper Article: "The Pain of Being Adult About A Parent's Death", 1993(5/3), Newspaper Article (Box-folder 007:009)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Newspaper Article: "A Solution for Countries Not Ready For Independence", 1993(5/6), Newspaper Article (Box-folder 007:010)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Newspaper Article: "UVa Co-Authors Examine the Many Faces of Mourning", 1993(6/4), Newspaper Clipping (Box-folder 007:011)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Newspaper Article: "Dealing with Death", 1993(6/10), Newspaper Clipping (Box-folder 007:012)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Newspaper Articles: "Racism That Wears A Multicultural Cloak", 1993(6/10), Newspaper Articles (Box-folder 007:013)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Newspaper Article: 1993(7/10), Newspaper Clipping (Box-folder 007:014)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Newspaper Article: 1993(7/19), Newspaper Clipping (Box-folder 007:015)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Newspaper Article: "Cleansing Ethnic Hatred", 1993(8), Newspaper Article (Box-folder 007:016)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Newspaper Article: "Russia Hates Troops' Exit in Baltics", 1993(8/23), Newspaper Article (Box-folder 007:017)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Newspaper Article: "Russian Troops in Lithuania", 1993(8/25), Newspaper Article (Box-folder 007:018)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Newspaper Article: "The Best Doctors in America", 1993(11), Newspaper Clipping (Box-folder 007:019)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Newspaper Article: 1993(11/16), Newspaper Article (Box-folder 007:020)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Magazine Article:"Preventive Therapy for War and Chaos", 1994(March/April), Magazine Article (Box-folder 007:021)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Newspaper Article: "Ethno-Nationalism Was Basis of Building Soviet States, Urbanovich Says", 1994(4/1), Newspaper Article (Box-folder 007:022)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Newspaper Article: "Amid Wars, Psychiatrists Seek Roots of Conflict", 1994(8/2), Newspaper Article (Box-folder 007:023)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Newspaper Article: "UVa Psychiatrist Finds Pattern in Ethnic Hatred", 1994(8/4), Newspaper Article (Box-folder 007:024)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Magazine Article: 1994(Autumn), Magazine Clipping (Box-folder 007:025)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Newspaper Article: 1994(10/28), Newspaper Clippings (Box-folder 007:026)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Newspaper Article: 1994(10/28), Newspaper Clippings (Box-folder 007:027)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Magazine Article: "Diplomats, Doctors and the End of the Cold War", 1994(10-11), Magazine Article (Box-folder 007:028)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Newspaper Article: 1995(1/12), Newspaper Article (Box-folder 007:029)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Newspaper Article: 1995(1/31), Newspaper Article (Box-folder 007:030)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Magazine Article: "Vamik Volkan Talks to Adeline Van Waning", 1995, Magazine Article (Box-folder 007:031)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Newspaper Article: "Going to the Heart of Estonian Conflict", 1995(1/14-31), Newspaper Clippings (Box-folder 007:032)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Newspaper Article: "Despite Soviet Occupation, Estonia Must Protect Rights of Its Russians", 1995(3/21), Newspaper Article (Box-folder 007:033)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Newspaper Article: "How Could Anyone Do That? Expert Gives an Answer", 1995(4/22), Newspaper Clippings (Box-folder 007:034)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Newspaper Article: "From Freud's Couch To Streets of Crown Heights", 1995(5/5), Newspaper Clippings (Box-folder 007:035)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Newspaper Article: "Reunion Recalls Days at Embassy in Kuwait", 1995(8/7), Newspaper Article (Box-folder 007:036)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Newspaper Article: "Kuwait Reunion", 1995(8/10), Newspaper Article (Box-folder 007:037)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Magazine Article: "The Diplomacy of Vamik Volkan", 1995(9), Magazine Article (Box-folder 007:038)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Newspaper Article: 1995(10/21), Newspaper Clipping (Box-folder 007:039)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Newspaper Article: 1995(11/8), Newspaper Clipping (Box-folder 007:040)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Newspaper Article: "Project Completed, Ambassador Makes Journey Back to Kuwait", 1995(11/28), Newspaper Article (Box-folder 007:041)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Newspaper Article: "University Faculty Dissipate Environmental, Ethnic Poisons in Estonia", 1995(12/1), Newspaper Article (Box-folder 007:042)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Newspaper Article: "US, Kuwait Ties to be Boosted", 1995(12/5), Newspaper Article (Box-folder 007:043)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Newspaper Article: "Volkan In Estonia", 1995(12/19-24), Newspaper Articles (Box-folder 007:044)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Magazine Article: "Hate in Our Own Background?", 1996(Spring), Magazine Clipping (Box-folder 007:045)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Magazine Article: "Interdisciplinary Center Develops Model for Peace", 1996(Spring), Magazine Clippings (Box-folder 007:046)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Newspaper Article: "'Peace Process Inevitable' Ex-Diplomat Tells Students", 1996(3/14), Newspaper Article (Box-folder 007:047)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Magazine Article: 1996(April), Magazine Article (Box-folder 007:048)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Newspaper Article: 1996, Newspaper Article (Box-folder 007:049)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Newspaper Article: "UVa to Help in Democratization of Estonia", 1996(4/10), Newspaper Article (Box-folder 007:050)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Magazine Article: "UVa Conflict Resolution Center Awarded Grant", 1996(4/12), Magazine Article (Box-folder 007:051)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Newspaper Article: "Friend Or Foe?", 1996(5/11), Newspaper Clipping (Box-folder 007:052)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Magazine Article: "Mind and Human Interaction", 1996(6), Magazine Articles (Box-folder 007:053)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Newspaper Article: "Closure Eludes Crash Victims' Families", 1996(6/17), Newspaper Article (Box-folder 007:054)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Newspaper Article: "Boyer Prize Awarded to Vamik Vokan", 1997(1), Newspaper Clipping (Box-folder 007:055)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Newspaper Article: 1997(1/3), Newspaper Article (Box-folder 007:056)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Newspaper Article: 1997(2), Newspaper Clippings (Box-folder 007:057)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Newspaper Article: 1997(2/4), Newspaper Clipping (Box-folder 007:058)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Newspaper Article: "Infromation Overload Treatens to Inaundage Art of Diplomacy, Panel Says", 1997(3/12), Newspaper Clipping (Box-folder 007:059)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Newspaper Article: "Volkan Received the L. Gryce Boyer Prize", 1997(5/2), Newspaper Clipping (Box-folder 007:060)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Magazine Article: 1997(6), Magazine Articles (Box-folder 007:061)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Newspaper Article: "Volkan Publishes Tow New Books", 1997(6/1), Newspaper Clippings (Box-folder 007:062)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Newspaper Article: 1997(7/7), Newspaper Articles (Box-folder 007:063)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Newspaper Article: 1997(8/7), Newspaper Clipping (Box-folder 007:064)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Newspaper Articles: 1997(7/8), Newspaper Articles (Box-folder 007:065)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Newspaper Article: "Publication Announcement - Bloodline", 1997(8/26-9/1), Newspaper Clipping (Box-folder 007:066)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Newspaper Article: 1997, Newspaper Article (Box-folder 007:067)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Newspaper Article: "GFocus on Reality", 1997(9/5), Newspaper Clippings (Box-folder 007:068)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Magazine Article: "Volkan Contributes Insights into Complexities of Nixon", 1997(9/28), Magazine Clippings (Box-folder 007:069)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Magazine Article: "Film Documents UVa Work in Resolving Age-Cold Conflicts", 1997(10/3), Magazine Clippings (Box-folder 007:070)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Newspaper Article: "Publication Announcement", 1997(11/2), Newspaper Clipping (Box-folder 007:071)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Newspaper Article: "Multi-Ethnic Ideal of the Soviet Union", 1997(11/9), Newspaper Article (Box-folder 007:072)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Magazine Article: "Home Sweet McGuillicuddy's", 1997(11/9), Magazine Clipping (Box-folder 007:073)